Guide to the Poly Archives Portrait Collection RG.028
Poly Archives at Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology
- P
  - Penn, Lynn S., undated (Box 6, Folder 142)
  - Penick, Joe E., undated (Box 6, Folder 143)
  - Pennell, Knowlton E., circa 1955 (Box 6, Folder 144)
  - Penrose, Charles, undated (Box 6, Folder 145)
  - Percy, undated (Box 6, Folder 146)
  - Perez, John, undated (Box 6, Folder 147)
  - Perl, Martin, 1993, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 148)
  - Perric, Lawrence J., undated (Box 6, Folder 149)
  - Peshchansky, Vera, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 150)
  - Peterson, Beth, undated (Box 6, Folder 151)
  - Peterson, N., undated (Box 6, Folder 152)
  - Peterson, Roland, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 153)
  - Petit, Philippe, 1974, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 154)
  - Petrucci, S., undated (Box 6, Folder 155)
  - Phillips, Donald, 1986, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 156)
  - Pickel, Paul F., undated (Box 6, Folder 157)
  - Pierce, John Robinson, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 158)
  - Pierre, Charles, undated (Box 6, Folder 159)
  - Pighi, Louis H., 1979 (Box 6, Folder 160)
  - Pignataro, Louis, 1975, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 161)
  - Pillai, S. Unnikrishna, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 162)
  - Pinkert, Dorothy M., undated (Box 6, Folder 163)
  - Piore, Emanuel, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 164)
  - Pittle, Marvin S., undated (Box 6, Folder 165)
  - Plympton, George W., circa 1900 (Box 6, Folder 166)
  - Poe, Alfred, undated (Box 6, Folder 167)
  - Pollack, Myron I., undated (Box 6, Folder 168)
  - Pomposello, Peter, undated (Box 6, Folder 169)
  - Pond [Podnossoff], Jules, circa 1930 (Box 6, Folder 170)
  - Posner, N., 1986 (Box 6, Folder 171)
  - Post, Benjamin, undated (Box 6, Folder 172)
  - Potts, Charles E., 1937, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 173)
  - Prassas, Elena, undated (Box 6, Folder 174)
  - Pratt, Edmund T., Jr., undated (Box 6, Folder 175)
  - Preiser, Stanley, 1969, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 176)
  - Prekeris, Algimantas, undated (Box 6, Folder 177)
  - Press, Jack J. (Box 6, Folder 178)
  - Preston, Richard, circa 1998 (Box 6, Folder 179)
  - Prieto, Robert, circa 1999 (Box 6, Folder 180)
  - Prill, Stanley, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 181)
  - Privalsky, Chuck, circa 1968 (Box 6, Folder 182)
  - Prohaska, Dorothy, undated (Box 6, Folder 183)
  - Proskauer, Eric S., 1978 (Box 6, Folder 184)
  - Protopapas, Angelos, undated (Box 6, Folder 185)
  - Puccinelli, undated (Box 6, Folder 186)
  - Puente, John, undated (Box 6, Folder 187)
  - Purcell, Joe, undated (Box 6, Folder 188)
  - Pyke, Geoffrey Nathaniel, undated (Box 6, Folder 189)
- Q
  - Qian, Jinghua, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Quaglino, James V., undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Queen, Nathaniel M., 1958 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - de Queiroz, Marcio S., undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Quinn, John, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Quirin, Edward J., 1966 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- R
  - Rabins, Michael J., undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Racz, Ernest, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Radden, Frank, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Rader, Charlies M., undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Rader, Lloyd F., undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Radovic, undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Ramberg, Eivind G.F., 1975 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Ramo, Simon, undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Rao, Bharat P., undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Rasmussen, E. Hart, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Rassier, Donald, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Ratay, Robert, undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Ratner, Bruce, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Ratti, Umberto, undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Raymond, John H., Rev, circa 1871 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Rechtschaffen, Bernard, circa 1983 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Reed, undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Rees, R. [G.], undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Regna, Peter P., undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Reichle, Leonard F.C., undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Reid, undated (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Reidy, Michael, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Reilly, Henry J., Gen., undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Reiser, Arnost, 1980s (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Reissner, Hans Jacob, undated (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Reitenbach, Nicholas, circa 1998 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Rennie, Richard, circa 1996 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Riccio, Anna Maria, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Richman, Jana (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Richmond, Martin R., undated (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Rickels, undated (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Riseborough, Peter S., undated (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Rittvo, Steve, undated (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Robbins, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Roberts, Arnie, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Roberts, Martin E., undated (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Robinson, Guner Suzek, undated (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A., undated (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Roden, Martin S., undated (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Rodriguez, Josephine, circa 1996 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Roess, Roger, undated (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Rogers, Harry Stanley (1890 - 1957) -- Youth, undated (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Rogers, Harry Stanley (1890 - 1957) -- Portraits, 1947, 1952, 1955, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Rogers, Harry Stanley (1890 - 1957) -- Events 1940-1957, 1940-1968 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Rogers, Harry Stanley (1890 - 1957) -- Events undated (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Rogers, Joel, undated (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Rogers, [Warren] L., Rev., undated (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Rogge, Herbert, undated (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Romanelli, Otto C., 1990s (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Romano, Frank, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Ronald, Mark (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Rorer, John, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Rosen, Bernard, undated (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Rosenberry, Walter S., undated (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Rosenthal, Myron, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Rosenthal, Saul W., 1955, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Rosenthal, Seymour, undated (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Rosenzweig, Carl, undated (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Ross, Gerald, undated (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Ross, Ian, undated (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Ross, Keith, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Rossoff, undated (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Roth, George Col., 1933 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Rothbard, Murray, undated (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Rothschild, Fred, undated (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Rothschild, Walter N., Jr., undated (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Rowley, Louis N., Jr., 1976, 1968, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Roy, Dipak, undated (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Ruben, Samuel, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Rubenstein, Charlie, undated (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Rubin (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Rudin, Paul, undated (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Ruppel, Alfred E., circa 1975 (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - Russell, Edward, 1954, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Russell, Joan, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - Russell, Jules, circa 1954 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Russell, William M. (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Russo, Onofrio "Nick", circa 1998 (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Ruten, William H., undated (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - Ryan, Albert J., Lt. Col., 1954-1955 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Ryan, John F., 1931 (Box 7, Folder 87)
- S
  - Sabavala, Darius, undated (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Sabet, M., undated (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - Sacher, Alex, undated (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - Sack, Edgar A., undated (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - Saidla, Leo E.A., 1952 (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - Sakai, Wataru, undated (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - Salkind, Alvin J., undated (Box 7, Folder 94)
  - Saltman, Bethany, undated (Box 7, Folder 95)
  - Salzinger, Kurt, 1982, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 96)
  - Sanator, Robert J., 1980, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 97)
  - Sannizjari, Salvatore, undated (Box 7, Folder 98)
  - Sarno, Frank J., undated (Box 7, Folder 99)
  - Savitt, Sidney A., 1983, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 100)
  - Sawyer, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 101)
  - Sawyer, Fred, undated (Box 7, Folder 102)
  - Sbasching, Richard W., 2001 (Box 7, Folder 103)
  - Sbordone, George J., undated (Box 7, Folder 104)
  - Schaaf, undated (Box 7, Folder 105)
  - Schachter, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 106)
  - Schaefer, John P., undated (Box 7, Folder 107)
  - Schaffner, Charles E., 1955 (Box 7, Folder 108)
  - Schallcross, Lewis, undated (Box 7, Folder 109)
  - Schatter, Arnie, undated (Box 7, Folder 110)
  - Schein, Eugene, undated (Box 7, Folder 111)
  - Scheiner, Lowell, undated (Box 7, Folder 112)
  - Scher, Seymour, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 113)
  - Schilling, Ronald, undated (Box 7, Folder 114)
  - Schillinger, A. George, undated (Box 7, Folder 115)
  - Schlect, Matt, undated (Box 7, Folder 116)
  - Schleher, Daniel Curtis, undated (Box 7, Folder 117)
  - Schleich, Donald, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 118)
  - Schleuning, Herbert W., undated (Box 7, Folder 119)
  - Schmidling, David, undated (Box 7, Folder 120)
  - Schmidt, Harry, undated (Box 7, Folder 121)
  - Schmidt, Jeanette, undated (Box 7, Folder 122)
  - Schroeder, Robert W., undated (Box 7, Folder 123)
  - Schuck, O. Hugo, undated (Box 7, Folder 124)
  - Schuck, Robert E., 1970 (Box 7, Folder 125)
  - Schurig, W. Fred, undated (Box 7, Folder 126)
  - Schuler, Raymond T., undated (Box 7, Folder 127)
  - Schuster, Seymour, undated (Box 7, Folder 128)
  - Schwalb, Allen J., 1995 (Box 7, Folder 129)
  - Schwalm, William H., undated (Box 7, Folder 130)
  - Schwartz, Jerome, undated (Box 7, Folder 131)
  - Scicutella, John, undated (Box 7, Folder 132)
  - Scott, C.F., undated (Box 7, Folder 133)
  - Scott, Shannon, undated (Box 7, Folder 134)
  - Seidenberg, Ivan, undated (Box 7, Folder 135)
  - Sekimoto, Tadahiro, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 136)
  - Selby, Harold E., 1960 (Box 7, Folder 137)
  - Selesnick, Ivan, undated (Box 7, Folder 138)
  - Senitzky, Benjamin, undated (Box 7, Folder 139)
  - Sepahbin, Amir H., undated (Box 7, Folder 140)
  - Setterstrom, Carl A., undated (Box 7, Folder 141)
  - Settle, Sandy, undated (Box 7, Folder 142)
  - Severance, Dennis (Box 7, Folder 143)
  - Sforza, Pasquale, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 144)
  - Shah, Chandni, undated (Box 7, Folder 145)
  - Shamis, Sidney S., undated (Box 7, Folder 146)
  - Shang, Joseph S., undated (Box 7, Folder 147)
  - Shapiro, Lawrence, undated (Box 7, Folder 148)
  - Shavers, Sgt., undated (Box 7, Folder 149)
  - Shaw, Leonard, 1986, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 150)
  - Sheldon, Rufus, undated (Box 7, Folder 151)
  - Sheldon, Samuel, undated (Box 7, Folder 152)
  - Shepherd, Donald S., 1980 (Box 7, Folder 153)
  - Sheverev, Valery, undated (Box 7, Folder 154)
  - Shields, B.A., undated (Box 7, Folder 155)
  - Shinn, Richard R, undated (Box 7, Folder 156)
  - Shmoys, Jerry, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 157)
  - Shnidman, Yitzahak, undated (Box 7, Folder 158)
  - Shooman, Martin, 1974, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 159)
  - Shultis, Christine, circa 1996 (Box 7, Folder 160)
  - Shustek, Leonard, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 161)
  - Sibner, Leslie, undated (Box 7, Folder 162)
  - Siderer, Jack, undated (Box 7, Folder 163)
  - Sie, John J., circa 1996 (Box 7, Folder 164)
  - Silber, Leo M., undated (Box 7, Folder 165)
  - Sill, Joshua Woodrow (1831-1862), undated (Box 7, Folder 166)
  - Silleck, Clarence F., 1963, 1983, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 167)
  - Silver, Sheldon, undated (Box 7, Folder 168)
  - Simanca, Santiago, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Simins, Herbert J., 1977 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Simmonds, G., undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Simo, Constance, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Singer, Gerald, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Singer, Henry, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Singer, Joel, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Sipress, Jack, circa 1995 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Sirota, Julius, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Sitock, George, 1950s (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Sivetz, Michael, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Sjuren, Harold, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Skrzypczak, Casmir, undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Skurla, George M., circa 1982 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Slack, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Slaughter, John B., undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Slutsky, Simon, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Slyke, Richard Van, undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Smith, E. B. L., undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Smith, Edward J., 1964 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Smith, Gregory D., undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Smith, Harrison, undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Smith, James M., 2000 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Smith, Joseph S., undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Smith, Kate, undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Smith, Stanley, undated (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Snitroff, Joseph, undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Snyder, Joel, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Soehngen, Henry F., undated (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Soffer, Jonathan, undated (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Sokolsky, Saul, undated (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Solimene, Nicholas, undated (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Sonnenfeldt, Richard, undated (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Soros, Paul, undated (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Soutar, Charles F., circa 1997 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Soviero, Joseph C., circa 1996 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Sparacino, Robert R., undated (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Spellane, Peter, undated (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Spenadel, Paul, undated (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Spencer, William J., 1987 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Sprinsky, William Lt. Col., undated (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Spruclt, Albert E., undated (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Squire, Edward J., 1956 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Stancu, Alina, undated (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - St. Lawrence, Jim, undated (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Steck, Paul G., undated (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Steele, Stuart, undated (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Stefanis, Anthony, undated (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Steigman, Joseph, undated (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Steil, Leonard, undated (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Stein, Richard S., undated (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Stein, Sidney J., undated (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Steinberg, Gerald M., 1956 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Steingut, Stanley, undated (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Steneck, Eugene, undated (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Sterling Drug, undated (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Sterling, Frank, undated (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Sterling, John, undated (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Stern, Henry Root, undated (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Sternberg, Sy, circa 2006 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Stevens, Joseph, undated (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Stever, H. Guyford, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Stidham, James A., 1956 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Stiel, Leonard, undated (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Stoll, Eric D., undated (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Stolze, William, 1959, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Stouraitis, Thanos, undated (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Strang, Charles D., 1985 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Strauss, Fred J., undated (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Strauss, Simon D., 1977, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Streubel, Ernest John, circa 1948 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Strom, Gordon, undated (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Strybing, Herman Frederick, 1880s (reproductions) (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Suarez, Humbert, undated (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Sudarsky, Jerry M., 1964, 1971, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Suel, Torsten, undated (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Sull, Won Bong, undated (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Sulzer, Henri G., undated (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Sun, Yun-Suan, undated (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Sung, Peter, circa 1987 (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Suttles, Sandy, undated (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Sviedrys, Romualdes, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - Swackhamer, Farris S., undated (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Swan, David, undated (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Swanson, Jeanne, undated (Box 8, Folder 85)
  - Swartz, Jerome, undated (Box 8, Folder 86)
  - Sweeney, Richard, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 87)
  - Sylvester, William R., circa 1980 (Box 8, Folder 88)
  - Szeglin, Arthur, undated (Box 8, Folder 89)
- T
  - Tai, Meihua, undated (Box 8, Folder 90)
  - Talberth, Henry, undated (Box 8, Folder 91)
  - Talley, Charles P., 1982 (Box 8, Folder 92)
  - Tam, Wai Nam, undated (Box 8, Folder 93)
  - Tamir, Theodor, undated (Box 8, Folder 94)
  - Teng, Hualiang (Harry), undated (Box 8, Folder 95)
  - Teraoka, Iwao, undated (Box 8, Folder 96)
  - Terzouli, Andrew J., undated (Box 8, Folder 97)
  - Tesoro, Giuliana, circa 1986 (Box 8, Folder 98)
  - Tevonian, Ronald, circa 1998 (Box 8, Folder 99)
  - Thevanayagam, Theva, undated (Box 8, Folder 100)
  - Thomas, Daniel J., 1950s (Box 8, Folder 101)
  - Thompson, Carol, undated (Box 8, Folder 102)
  - Thompson, Harley, undated (Box 8, Folder 103)
  - Thompson, Michael, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 104)
  - Thorne, undated (Box 8, Folder 105)
  - Thorsen, Richard, 1980, 1986, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 106)
  - Throndsen, Elton C., 1955 (Box 8, Folder 107)
  - Thurber, Elmer, undated (Box 8, Folder 108)
  - Tobias, Abraham Joel, 1960s (Box 8, Folder 109)
  - Todd, Leonard, undated (Box 8, Folder 110)
  - Tongobarch, Vincent, undated (Box 8, Folder 111)
  - Tooney, Nancy, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 112)
  - Topfer, Morton L., 2001 (Box 8, Folder 113)
  - Torn, Laurence, undated (Box 8, Folder 114)
  - Towl, Ted, 1911 (Box 8, Folder 115)
  - Townsend, Paul B., undated (Box 8, Folder 116)
  - Trabold, Andrew Frank, undated (Box 8, Folder 117)
  - Tran, Duong, undated (Box 8, Folder 118)
  - Trani, John M., 1993 (Box 8, Folder 119)
  - Trump, John George, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 120)
  - Truxal, John, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 121)
  - Tsang, Andy, circa 2005 (Box 8, Folder 122)
  - Tsao, Robert H. C., circa 1997 (Box 8, Folder 123)
  - Tsifrinovich, Vladimir, undated (Box 8, Folder 124)
  - Tsotras, Vassilis J., undated (Box 8, Folder 125)
  - Tucker, Marion, undated (Box 8, Folder 126)
  - Tully, John, undated (Box 8, Folder 127)
  - Turaun, George A., circa 1954 (Box 8, Folder 128)
  - Turi, Edith, 1996, circa 2000 (Box 8, Folder 129)
  - Turiel, David, undated (Box 8, Folder 130)
  - Tzes, Anthony P., undated (Box 8, Folder 131)
- U
  - Ughetta, Henry L., undated (Box 8, Folder 132)
  - Ugwa, Okay, undated (Box 8, Folder 133)
  - Ujazdowski, T. J., undated (Box 8, Folder 134)
  - Ullman, Robert, undated (Box 8, Folder 135)
  - Ulman, Abraham, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 136)
  - Ulman, Hanna A., undated (Box 8, Folder 137)
  - Umanskiy, Vladimir, undated (Box 8, Folder 138)
  - Ungar, J. Stephen, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 139)
  - Uzun, Necdet, undated (Box 8, Folder 140)
- V
  - Vacca, Louis N., undated (Box 8, Folder 141)
  - Vafakos, William P., 1978 (Box 8, Folder 142)
  - Valle, Fabio Della, undated (Box 8, Folder 143)
  - Van Cook, Charles F., undated (Box 8, Folder 144)
  - Van Horn, John R., undated (Box 8, Folder 145)
  - Van Norden, E. M., 1955 (Box 8, Folder 146)
  - Van Slyke, Richard, undated (Box 8, Folder 147)
  - Van Wagenen, Lindsey, undated (Box 8, Folder 148)
  - Van Wie, Jonathan, undated (Box 8, Folder 149)
  - Van Wynen, Kenneth, undated (Box 8, Folder 150)
  - Varmis, undated (Box 8, Folder 151)
  - Vathke, Otto W., undated (Box 8, Folder 152)
  - Veeraraghavan, Malathi, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 153)
  - Veit, Robert C., circa 1966 (Box 8, Folder 154)
  - Velazquez, Nydia, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 155)
  - Vembenil, Juby, circa 1996 (Box 8, Folder 156)
  - Vemuri, Murali K., undated (Box 8, Folder 157)
  - Venner, Julius, undated (Box 8, Folder 158)
  - Vermilye, Rodney J., undated (Box 8, Folder 159)
  - Vesce, V.C., undated (Box 8, Folder 160)
  - Viets, Herman, circa 1995 (Box 8, Folder 161)
  - Vignola, Paul, undated (Box 8, Folder 162)
  - Villa, S. Santos, undated (Box 8, Folder 163)
  - Vincent, Patrick J., undated (Box 8, Folder 164)
  - Vineyard, George, circa 1978 (Box 8, Folder 165)
  - Viola, Frank J., undated (Box 8, Folder 166)
  - Voci, Frank, undated (Box 8, Folder 167)
  - Vogel, Alice, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 168)
  - Vogl, Otto, circa 1982, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 169)
  - Voltz, Peter, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 170)
  - Von Karmen, Theodore, undated (Box 8, Folder 171)
  - VonPuttkamer, Jesco H., undated (Box 8, Folder 172)
  - Vradis, George C., circa 1995 (Box 8, Folder 173)
  - Vulanti, Thomas, undated (Box 8, Folder 174)
  - Vybiral, undated (Box 8, Folder 175)
- W
  - Waddell, Russell, circa 1954 (Box 8, Folder 176)
  - Wagman, Jack, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 177)
  - Wagner, Robert, circa 1975 (Box 8, Folder 178)
  - Walker, Burt, undated (Box 8, Folder 179)
  - Walker, W.F., circa 1960 (Box 8, Folder 180)
  - Wallace, Richard, circa 1955 (Box 8, Folder 181)
  - Wallau, Herman Leon, circa 1954 (Box 8, Folder 182)
  - Wallach, Steven J., undated (Box 8, Folder 183)
  - Wallach, Victor, undated (Box 8, Folder 184)
  - Waller, Henry, undated (Box 8, Folder 185)
  - Waller (nee Lepow), Sylvia, circa 1999 (Box 8, Folder 186)
  - Walsh, Charles E., undated (Box 8, Folder 187)
  - Walsh, John, undated (Box 8, Folder 188)
  - Walsh, undated (Box 8, Folder 189)
  - Walter, William T., undated (Box 8, Folder 190)
  - Walton, Robert E., undated (Box 8, Folder 191)
  - Wandmacher, F. Cornelius, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 192)
  - Wang, Jiun-Nan (Jim), undated (Box 8, Folder 193)
  - Wang, Xiaodong, undated (Box 8, Folder 194)
  - Wang, Yao, circa 1997 (Box 8, Folder 195)
  - Warren, Helen, 1978, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 196)
  - Wasilchuk, Steven, undated (Box 8, Folder 197)
  - Wasserman, Steven, undated (Box 8, Folder 198)
  - Waterman, Alan T., circa 1962 (Box 8, Folder 199)
  - Watson, Lester W., circa 1959 (Box 8, Folder 200)
  - Weaver, Stanley A., circa 1932 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Weber, Ernst (1901-1966), undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Weber, Sonya, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Wechsler, Harry C., 1981 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Wegrzyn, Stanley W., undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Weil, Edward, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Weil, Robert T., Jr., undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Weill, George, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Weiman, David N., undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Wein, Joel, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Weindling, Ralph E., circa 1998 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Weinman, Eugene A., undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Weiner, James R., undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Weintraub, Ruth, undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Weintraub, Stanley B., undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Weiser, Sidney, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Weiss, Gerald, undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Weiss, Marvin D., undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Weissberger, A., undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Weisstuch, Donald N., 1999, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Welch, Herbert, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Wellbrock, Richard, undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Wendt, undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Wendt, Arthur S., undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Wener, Richard, undated (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Wentzel, Lewis A., circa 1937 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Wenzel, Alfred C., undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Weseman, Edwin J., circa 1939 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - West, Warren J., circa 1966 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Westermann, David, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Whalen, Robert J., undated (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Whang, Sung, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Whang (brothers), circa 1955 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Wheeler, Harold A., circa 1996 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Whidden, James T., 1956 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Whipple, Clyde, circa 1955, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Whipple, Melville C., undated (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - White, George R., undated (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - White, J.L., undated (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - White, William Augustus, photocopies of 1880 photo (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Whitehead, Herbert G., undated (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Whitley, Arthur F., undated (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Whitmore, Carl, circa 1953 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Whitmore, Willet F., undated (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Wich, Emil A., undated (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Widnall, Sheila, undated (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Wieber, George A., undated (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Wiederhorn, Norman, undated (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Wiedersum, Frederic G., undated (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Wiegand, Dick, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Wiener, Anthony J., undated (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Wigner, Eugene Paul, undated (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Wikstrand, William C., undated (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Wilcken, Henry J., undated (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Wilcox, George L. (1915-2002), 1953 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Wildermuth, Gordon, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Williams, Blair, undated (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Williams, Dennis C., undated (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Williams, Frank H., 0196-1961 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Williams, Robert P., Lieutenant, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Willig, George H., 1977 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Wilson, Robert E., 1940 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Winkert, John W., circa 1951 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Winsche, Warren, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Winters, Warrinton, undated (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Wishert, John C., Major, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 66)